or gross.
或者说，真恶心。
But you can see how heated this is getting.
但你可以看到这事儿吵得有多白热化了。
Clearly, Maga is much more divided about whether to overthrow Iran than they were about
很明显，在“是否要推翻伊朗”这个问题上，MAGA阵营的分歧
whether to overthrow America.
比他们当初在“是否要推翻美国”时大多了。
Every little comment in this interview turned into a semantic battle.
这次采访里的每句评论，都演变成了一场文字游戏。
Really believe that.
我真信了。
We're carrying out military strikes today.
我们今天正在执行军事打击。
You said Israel was.
你刚才说“是Israel”。
Right.
对。
With our help.
有我们帮忙。
I'm said we, Israel is leading them, but we're supporting them.
我说的是“我们”，是Israel在主导，但我们在支援。
Well, this, you're breaking news here because the US government last night denied the
哦，你这可是爆了个大料啊，因为美国政府昨晚刚否认了，
National Security Council spokesman Alex Fifer denied on behalf of Trump that we were acting
国家安全委员会的发言人Alex Fifer代表Trump否认了我们代表Israel
on Israel's behalf in any offensive capacity.
采取了任何进攻性行动。
We're not bombing them.
我们没有在轰炸他们。
Israel's bombing them.
是Israel在轰炸他们。
You just said we were.
你刚才明明说“我们”了。
We are supporting Israel as a state.
我们是在支援Israel这个国家。
We?
我们？
I?
我？
You?
你？
For the party that promised no confusion around pronouns, this is really confusing.
对于一个信誓旦旦要在“代词”问题上绝不搞混的政党来说，这可真是乱得可以啊。
The point is, Maga World is tearing itself apart and everyone is waiting for Trump to
重点是，MAGA世界正在疯狂窝里斗，所有人都在等着Trump
make a decision.
做决定。
And remember, Trump abruptly left the G7 summit so he could rush back to the White House,
记住，Trump可是突然退出了G7峰会，就为了火速赶回白宫，
meet with his national security team in the situation room, and decide if he's bringing
和他的国安团队在战情室开会，然后决定是否要
America into this war.
把美国拖入这场战争。
So, we were all waiting for the big announcement.
所以，我们都在屏息以待那个重磅官宣。
And then it came.
然后，它来了。
Trump sat in the truth social post.
Trump在他的“真相社交”上发帖说：
It is my great honor to announce that I will be putting up two beautiful flag poles on
“我非常荣幸地宣布，我将会在白宫的两侧，
both sides of the White House and North and South Lawns.
也就是南草坪和北草坪上，竖起两根漂亮的旗杆。”
Yes, that is definitely an announcement.
是的，这绝对算是个“官宣”。
Not the announcement we were waiting for, but sure, have a couple flag poles installed
虽然不是我们等候的那个，但行吧，在白宫装几根旗杆就装吧。
at the White House.
在白宫。
That'll be something for the groundskeepers to take care of while you're busy in the
这样当您在战情室里忙着处理更重要的大事时，
situation room dealing with more important matters.
园丁们也总算有活儿干了。
At 11 o'clock we're lifting the flag, but we're going to lift the pole now and then
“11点钟我们会升旗，但我们现在先把杆子立起来，然后
they're going to the other side.
他们再去另一边。”
OK, all right, be out there introducing the whole thing.
“好的，好的，我会亲自到场介绍这一切。”
Now, back to the situation room.
“现在，回到战情室。”
So we'll have one on this side of the building.
“所以我们大楼这边会有一根，”
We'll have one on that side of the building properly placed.
“那一边也有一根，位置都摆得很好。”
These are the best poles anywhere in the country, in the world, actually.
“这些是全美国，不，实际上是全世界最棒的旗杆。”
They're tapered.
“它们是锥形的。”
They have the nice top.
“顶部也很好看。”
And I don't know if you people are aesthetic.
“我不知道你们这些人有没有审美。”
They're the fake news.
“他们是假新闻。”
I don't know about that.
“那个我不好说。”
I don't know there, but it's a very exciting project to meet.
“我不知道他们，但对我来说，这是个非常激动人心的项目。”
What's going on here?
这到底是什么情况？
Feels like someone told him, sir, you're not doing well in the poles.
感觉就像有人跟他说：“先生，您在‘民调’(polls)里的数据不太好看。”
And he was like, I hear you, I'm on it.
然后他回答：“我懂了，这事我门儿清。” (注：此处为英文双关语，民调polls和旗杆poles同音)
By the way, what was that aside about how the fake news doesn't understand flag pole
话说回来，他那句关于“假新闻”不懂旗杆美学的
aesthetics?
旁白是几个意思？
I mean, this is a whole new stereotype of the liberal media I didn't even know about.
我的天，这简直是给自由派媒体打造了一个我闻所未闻的全新刻板印象。
They live on Hunter Biden's laptop, and they have no appreciation for tapered flag poles.
“他们整天就惦记着Hunter Biden的笔记本电脑，而且对锥形旗杆没有半点欣赏水平。”
Now, personally, I think it's cool that Trump found a new use for the 50-foot pole
不过，个人觉得Trump总算给那根50英尺长、
that Melania refuses to touch him with.
Melania死活不肯碰他的长杆找到了新用处，还挺酷的。
He was clearly having a good time.
他显然玩得很开心。
Although he stopped himself from getting too carried away.
尽管他还是克制住了自己，没让自己太得意忘形。
Let's have a good decoder lifting.
“让我们来一次体面的‘升杆’仪式。”
They also use another word, but I'm not going to use that word.
“他们也用另一个词，不过我可不用那个词。”
Do you know that it is?
“你知道是哪个词吧？”
The word is such within e.
“那个词是以E开头的。”
Do you know what the word is?
“你们知道是什么词吧？”
If I ever used it, I'd be run out of town by you.
“我要是用了，你们这帮媒体早就把我轰出去了。”